Ronel De Jesus

dejesusronel29@gmail.com 045 Control Telacsan, Macabebe, Philippines

+639357249128 https://ronel-dejesus.netlify.app/

PROFILE

Experienced web developer in full-stack development. I focus on creating top-quality websites and applications, making sure users have a great experience. I work well with diverse teams to meet project goals. My track record proves my commitment to delivering excellent results that exceed expectations. I bring a mix of technical skills and a passion for innovation to every project, aiming to simplify complexities and enhance user satisfaction. Let's collaborate to bring creativity and precision to your development needs.

EDUCATION

Don Honorio Ventura State University | Bacolor, Philippines **BS** Computer Engineering

June 2018 - August 2022

INTERNSHIP

MGHS Solutions and Advertising Services | City of Tarlac, Philippines

My Position: Software Engineer/ Web & App Developer

Business Head: Mary Grace A. Hizon Telegram: Contact @MsGraceBH

April 2022 - July 2022

October 2022 - Present

EXPERIENCE

LH & Creatives | Makati City, Philippines

Website: https://lionheart.asia/en/

My Position: Junior Web Developer

- Develop and maintained responsive design web app
- Successfully delivered multiple WordPress-based websites for Japanese clients, resulting in increased online visibility and user engagement.
- Collaborated closely with Japanese directors and designers to understand their specific requirements and preferences, ensuring the delivery of tailor-made web solutions.
- Strong command of JavaScript programming language for creating dynamic and interactive web applications.

ONLINE COURSES

Certification: https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/lenor/responsive-web-design

Simplilearn | Karnataka, India.

July 2022 - July 2022

Introduction to HTML

Certification: https://simpli-web.app.link/e/BJsJGw6Oxsb

Simplilearn | Karnataka, India.

July 2022 - July 2022

Introduction to CSS

Certification: https://simpli-web.app.link/e/30CzquiPxsb

TECH STACKS

Front end: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SASS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, React JS, Next JS

Back end: PHP, Node JS, Express, MongoDB, MySQL

• Hosting: Vercel, Netlify, Github

• CMS: Wordpress, Fegg(php framework)

• Others: Git, Adobe Xd, React Redux

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Communication Skills:

- Clear and concise written and verbal communication
- Active listening skills
- Ability to convey complex ideas in a straight forward manner

Time management:

- Effective priorization of tasks
- Proven ability to meet deadlines
- Efficient use of time and resources

Self-Motivation:

- Demonstrated ability to work independently
- Proactive approach to tasks and problem solving Results-driven mindset

Adaptability:

- Flexibility in handling changes and unexpected challenges
- Openness to new tools and technologies